var quizArray = [{
		"id":"0",
		"question":"Fear of animals",
		"choice1":"Vestiphobia",
		"choice2":"Topophobia",
		"choice3":"Zoophobia",
		"choice4":"Zelophobia",
		"correct":"Zoophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"1",
		"question":"Fear of words",
		"choice1":"Xylophobia",
		"choice2":"Verbophobia",
		"choice3":"Verminophobia",
		"choice4":"Sociophobia",
		"correct":"Verbophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"2",
		"question":"Fear of looking up",
		"choice1":"Felinophobia",
		"choice2":"Chaetophobia",
		"choice3":"Batophobia",
		"choice4":"Anablephobia",
		"correct":"Anablephobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"3",
		"question":"Fear of men",
		"choice1":"Maieusiophobia",
		"choice2":"Menophobia",
		"choice3":"Androphobia",
		"choice4":"Botanophobia",
		"correct":"Androphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"4",
		"question":"Fear of floods",
		"choice1":"Antlophobia",
		"choice2":"Carnophobia",
		"choice3":"Dikephobia",
		"choice4":"Dipsophobia",
		"correct":"Antlophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"5",
		"question":"Fear of being dirty",
		"choice1":"Gymnophobia",
		"choice2":"Automysophobia",
		"choice3":"Heliophobia",
		"choice4":"Entomophobia",
		"correct":"Automysophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"6",
		"question":"Fear of bacteria",
		"choice1":"Microphobia",
		"choice2":"Verminophobia",
		"choice3":"Genophobia",
		"choice4":"Bacteriophobia",
		"correct":"Bacteriophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"7",
		"question":"Fear of heights or being close to high buildings",
		"choice1":"Felinophobia",
		"choice2":"Batophobia",
		"choice3":"Sophophobia",
		"choice4":"Spermatophobia",
		"correct":"Batophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"8",
		"question":"Fear of books",
		"choice1":"Bibliophobia",
		"choice2":"Coulrophobia",
		"choice3":"Katsaridaphobia",
		"choice4":"Antlophobia",
		"correct":"Bibliophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"9",
		"question":"Fear of plants",
		"choice1":"Rectophobia",
		"choice2":"Botanophobia",
		"choice3":"Automysophobia",
		"choice4":"Proctophobia",
		"correct":"Botanophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"10",
		"question":"Fear of ugliness",
		"choice1":"Selachophobia",
		"choice2":"Ochophobia",
		"choice3":"Cacophobia",
		"choice4":"Dipsophobia",
		"correct":"Cacophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"11",
		"question":"Fear of meat",
		"choice1":"Carnophobia",
		"choice2":"Macrophobia",
		"choice3":"Lygophobia",
		"choice4":"Kathisophobia",
		"correct":"Carnophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"12",
		"question":"Fear of hair",
		"choice1":"Epistemophobia",
		"choice2":"Hematophobia",
		"choice3":"Chaetophobia",
		"choice4":"Hadephobia",
		"correct":"Chaetophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"13",
		"question":"Fear of dancing",
		"choice1":"Chorophobia",
		"choice2":"Claustrophobia",
		"choice3":"Gymnophobia",
		"choice4":"Dendrophobia",
		"correct":"Chorophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"14",
		"question":"Fear of confined spaces.",
		"choice1":"Judeophobia",
		"choice2":"Ideophobia",
		"choice3":"Claustrophobia",
		"choice4":"Clinophobia",
		"correct":"Claustrophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"15",
		"question":"Fear of going to bed",
		"choice1":"Batrachophobia",
		"choice2":"Clinophobia",
		"choice3":"Ichthyophobia",
		"choice4":"Ceraunophobia",
		"correct":"Clinophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"16",
		"question":"Fear of comets",
		"choice1":"Methyphobia",
		"choice2":"Meteophobia",
		"choice3":"Selachophobia",
		"choice4":"Cometophobia",
		"correct":"Cometophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"17",
		"question":"Fear of clowns",
		"choice1":"Coulrophobia",
		"choice2":"Chemophobia",
		"choice3":"Catapedaphobia",
		"choice4":"Dermatophobia",
		"correct":"Coulrophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"18",
		"question":"Fear of trees",
		"choice1":"Leukophobia",
		"choice2":"Botanophobia",
		"choice3":"Dendrophobia",
		"choice4":"Catapedaphobia",
		"correct":"Dendrophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"19",
		"question":"Fear of dentists",
		"choice1":"Felinophobia",
		"choice2":"Emetophobia",
		"choice3":"Dextrophobia",
		"choice4":"Dentophobia",
		"correct":"Dentophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"20",
		"question":"Fear of justice",
		"choice1":"Dikephobia",
		"choice2":"Frigophobia",
		"choice3":"Levophobia",
		"choice4":"Maniaphobia",
		"correct":"Dikephobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"21",
		"question":"Fear of drinking",
		"choice1":"Nebulaphobia",
		"choice2":"Botanophobia",
		"choice3":"Dipsophobia",
		"choice4":"Megalophobia",
		"correct":"Dipsophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"22",
		"question":"Fear of insects",
		"choice1":"Entomophobia",
		"choice2":"Vestiphobia",
		"choice3":"Euphobia",
		"choice4":"Ideophobia",
		"correct":"Entomophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"23",
		"question":"Fear of knowledge",
		"choice1":"Ideophobia",
		"choice2":"Epistemophobia",
		"choice3":"Myrmecophobia",
		"choice4":"Neopharmaphobia",
		"correct":"Epistemophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"24",
		"question":"Fear of hearing good news",
		"choice1":"Verminophobia",
		"choice2":"Ochlophobia",
		"choice3":"Emetophobia",
		"choice4":"Euphobia",
		"correct":"Euphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"25",
		"question":"Fear of cats",
		"choice1":"Nudophobia",
		"choice2":"Felinophobia",
		"choice3":"Panthophobia",
		"choice4":"Phallophobia",
		"correct":"Felinophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"26",
		"question":"Fear of laughter",
		"choice1":"Geliophobia",
		"choice2":"Phasmophobia",
		"choice3":"Rectophobia",
		"choice4":"Vestiphobia",
		"correct":"Geliophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"27",
		"question":"Fear of sex",
		"choice1":"Genophobia",
		"choice2":"Heliophobia",
		"choice3":"Genitaphobia",
		"choice4":"Sciophobia",
		"correct":"Genophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"28",
		"question":"Fear of nudity",
		"choice1":"Tomophobia",
		"choice2":"Coulrophobia",
		"choice3":"Nudophobia",
		"choice4":"Gymnophobia",
		"correct":"Nudophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"29",
		"question":"Fear of hell",
		"choice1":"Stenophobia",
		"choice2":"Hadephobia",
		"choice3":"Dipsophobia",
		"choice4":"Heliophobia",
		"correct":"Hadephobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"30",
		"question":"Fear of sinning",
		"choice1":"Alektrophobia",
		"choice2":"Hamartophobia",
		"choice3":"Toxiphobia",
		"choice4":"Uranophobia",
		"correct":"Hamartophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"31",
		"question":"Fear of the sun.",
		"choice1":"Lunaphobia",
		"choice2":"Heliophobia",
		"choice3":"Solarophobia",
		"choice4":"Neophobia",
		"correct":"Heliophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"32",
		"question":"Fear of long words",
		"choice1":"Quedicopopotaverbolapiticusophobia",
		"choice2":"Calorobiticusvertoconosisequilaphobia",
		"choice3":"Hippopotomonstrosesquipedaliophobia",
		"choice4":"Vexiuranosispedilaphobia",
		"correct":"Hippopotomonstrosesquipedaliophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"33",
		"question":"Fear of water",
		"choice1":"Pyrophobia",
		"choice2":"Hydrophobia",
		"choice3":"Aquanophobia",
		"choice4":"Carbonophobia",
		"correct":"Hydrophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"34",
		"question":"Fear of blood",
		"choice1":"Platelophobia",
		"choice2":"Hematophobia",
		"choice3":"Carbonophobia",
		"choice4":"Dipsophobia",
		"correct":"Hematophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"35",
		"question":"Fear of fish",
		"choice1":"Ichthyophobia",
		"choice2":"Malansophobia",
		"choice3":"Somniphobia",
		"choice4":"Ranidaphobia",
		"correct":"Ichthyophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"36",
		"question":"Fear of insects",
		"choice1":"Parasitophobia",
		"choice2":"Insectophobia",
		"choice3":"Centophobia",
		"choice4":"Arachinophobia",
		"correct":"Insectophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"37",
		"question":"Fear of failure or defeat",
		"choice1":"Hematophobia",
		"choice2":"Reconaphobia",
		"choice3":"Cocarophobia",
		"choice4":"Kakorrhaphiophobia",
		"correct":"Kakorrhaphiophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"38",
		"question":"Fear of cockroaches",
		"choice1":"Kathisophobia",
		"choice2":"Katsaridaphobia",
		"choice3":"Baygonophobia",
		"choice4":"Insectophobia",
		"correct":"Katsaridaphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"39",
		"question":"Fear of stealing",
		"choice1":"Kleptophobia",
		"choice2":"Koinoniphobia",
		"choice3":"Leukophobia",
		"choice4":"Medomalacuphobia",
		"correct":"Kleptophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"40",
		"question":"Fear of rooms",
		"choice1":"Koniophobia",
		"choice2":"Suitophobia",
		"choice3":"Nyctophobia",
		"choice4":"Koinoniphobia",
		"correct":"Koinoniphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"41",
		"question":"Fear of dust",
		"choice1":"Dustrophobia",
		"choice2":"Koniophobia",
		"choice3":"Osmophobia",
		"choice4":"Pediophobia",
		"correct":"Koniophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"42",
		"question":"Fear of the color white",
		"choice1":"Leukophobia",
		"choice2":"Pediophobia",
		"choice3":"Heterophobia",
		"choice4":"Westenophobia",
		"correct":"Leukophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"43",
		"question":"Fear of lakes",
		"choice1":"Lekrophobia",
		"choice2":"Limnophobia",
		"choice3":"Lyssophobia",
		"choice4":"Dustrophobia",
		"correct":"Limnophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"44",
		"question":"Fear of computers",
		"choice1":"Technophobia",
		"choice2":"Procesophobia",
		"choice3":"Iconaphobia",
		"choice4":"Logizomechanophobia",
		"correct":"Logizomechanophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"45",
		"question":"Fear of words",
		"choice1":"Logophobia",
		"choice2":"Verbaphobia",
		"choice3":"Linguinophobia",
		"choice4":"Leteranophobia",
		"correct":"Logophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"46",
		"question":"Fear of darkness",
		"choice1":"Dimenophobia",
		"choice2":"Lyssophobia",
		"choice3":"Dipsophobia",
		"choice4":"Emetophobia",
		"correct":"Lygophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"47",
		"question":"Fear of cooking",
		"choice1":"Cookieraphobia",
		"choice2":"Nigerophobia",
		"choice3":"Mageirocophobia",
		"choice4":"Pagophobia",
		"correct":"Mageirocophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"48",
		"question":"Fear of childbirth",
		"choice1":"Birthophobia",
		"choice2":"Calaystophobia",
		"choice3":"Genitaphobia",
		"choice4":"Maieusiophobia",
		"correct":"Maieusiophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"49",
		"question":"Fear of machines",
		"choice1":"Eletrophobia",
		"choice2":"Machinasophobia",
		"choice3":"Mechanophobia",
		"choice4":"Sciophobia",
		"correct":"Mechanophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"50",
		"question":"Fear of large things",
		"choice1":"Giganthrophobia",
		"choice2":"Hydrophobia",
		"choice3":"Lumisophobia",
		"choice4":"Megalophobia",
		"correct":"Megalophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"51",
		"question":"Fear of the color black",
		"choice1":"Melanophobia",
		"choice2":"Blackiephobia",
		"choice3":"Dimnophobia",
		"choice4":"Catastrophobia",
		"correct":"Melanophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"52",
		"question":"Fear of metal",
		"choice1":"Rustyphobia",
		"choice2":"Bacaliophobia",
		"choice3":"Metallophobia",
		"choice4":"Ironophobia",
		"correct":"Metallophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"53",
		"question":"Fear of alcohol",
		"choice1":"Nelophobia",
		"choice2":"Linonophobia",
		"choice3":"Mastigophobia",
		"choice4":"Methyphobia",
		"correct":"Methyphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"54",
		"question":"Fear of small things",
		"choice1":"Smaliophobia",
		"choice2":"Giganthrophobia",
		"choice3":"Megalophobia",
		"choice4":"Microphobia",
		"correct":"Microphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"55",
		"question":"Fear of myths or stories",
		"choice1":"Achaeophobia",
		"choice2":"Mythophobia",
		"choice3":"Cleophobia",
		"choice4":"Mythophobia",
		"correct":"Mythophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"56",
		"question":"Fear of death or dead things",
		"choice1":"Macrophobia",
		"choice2":"Necrophobia",
		"choice3":"Thanatophobia",
		"choice4":"Alicophobia",
		"correct":"Necrophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"57",
		"question":"Fear of clouds",
		"choice1":"Cumuluphobia",
		"choice2":"Neophobia",
		"choice3":"Nephophobia",
		"choice4":"Nimbusophobia",
		"correct":"Nephophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"58",
		"question":"Fear of the night",
		"choice1":"Noctiphobia",
		"choice2":"Necrophobia",
		"choice3":"Uranophobia",
		"choice4":"Nosocomephobia",
		"correct":"Noctiphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"59",
		"question":"Fear of names",
		"choice1":"Nomatophobia",
		"choice2":"Identophobia",
		"choice3":"Nemophobia",
		"choice4":"Nomatophobia",
		"correct":"Nomatophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"60",
		"question":"Fear of nuclear weapons",
		"choice1":"Kataliophobia",
		"choice2":"Hazardophobia",
		"choice3":"Nucleomituphobia",
		"choice4":"Biophobia",
		"correct":"Nucleomituphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"61",
		"question":"Fear of numbers",
		"choice1":"Numerophobia",
		"choice2":"Katagelophobia",
		"choice3":"Isopterophobia",
		"choice4":"Hylephobia",
		"correct":"Numerophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"62",
		"question":"Fear of gaining weight",
		"choice1":"Thinophobia",
		"choice2":"Obesophobia",
		"choice3":"Meganophobia",
		"choice4":"Verbophobia",
		"correct":"Obesophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"63",
		"question":"Fear of vehicles",
		"choice1":"Ochophobia",
		"choice2":"Catallophobia",
		"choice3":"Alicophobia",
		"choice4":"Felinophobia",
		"correct":"Ochophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"64",
		"question":"Fear of dreams",
		"choice1":"Scoleciphobia",
		"choice2":"Oneirophobia",
		"choice3":"Nightophobia",
		"choice4":"Destrophobia",
		"correct":"Oneirophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"65",
		"question":"Fear of birds",
		"choice1":"Avianophobia",
		"choice2":"Ornithophobia",
		"choice3":"Wingophobia",
		"choice4":"Fetherophobia",
		"correct":"Ornithophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"66",
		"question":"Fear of ice or frost",
		"choice1":"Refostrophobia",
		"choice2":"Pagophobia",
		"choice3":"Fetherophobia",
		"choice4":"Colosustrophobia",
		"correct":"Pagophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"67",
		"question":"Fear of paper",
		"choice1":"Cylophobia",
		"choice2":"Scoleciphobia",
		"choice3":"Papyrophobia",
		"choice4":"Reconaphobia",
		"correct":"Papyrophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"68",
		"question":"Fear of parasites",
		"choice1":"Parasitophobia",
		"choice2":"Insectophobia",
		"choice3":"Anablephobia",
		"choice4":"Sciophobia",
		"correct":"Parasitophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"69",
		"question":"Fear of dolls",
		"choice1":"Necrophobia",
		"choice2":"Nephophobia",
		"choice3":"Pediophobia",
		"choice4":"Manequiphobia",
		"correct":"Pediophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"70",
		"question":"Fear of children",
		"choice1":"Philophobia",
		"choice2":"Pedophobia",
		"choice3":"Claustrophobia",
		"choice4":"Kleptophobia",
		"correct":"Pedophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"71",
		"question":"Fear of poverty",
		"choice1":"Peniaphobia",
		"choice2":"Provostrophobia",
		"choice3":"Selachophobia",
		"choice4":"Mageirocophobia",
		"correct":"Peniaphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"72",
		"question":"Fear of anything new",
		"choice1":"Minostrophobia",
		"choice2":"Macrophobia",
		"choice3":"Neophobia",
		"choice4":"Neopharmaphobia",
		"correct":"Neophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"73",
		"question":"Fear of urine or urinating",
		"choice1":"Urinostrophobia",
		"choice2":"Pedostrophobia",
		"choice3":"Xenophobia",
		"choice4":"Urophobia",
		"correct":"Urophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"74",
		"question":"Fear of disease",
		"choice1":"Sciophobia",
		"choice2":"Coloquiophobia",
		"choice3":"Pathophobia",
		"choice4":"Destrophobia",
		"correct":"Pathophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"75",
		"question":"Fear of childbirth",
		"choice1":"Batophobia",
		"choice2":"Anablephobia",
		"choice3":"Parturiphobia",
		"choice4":"Pestophobia",
		"correct":"Parturiphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"76",
		"question":"Fear of gold",
		"choice1":"Metallophobia",
		"choice2":"Golicostrophobia",
		"choice3":"Aurophobia",
		"choice4":"Bacallophobia",
		"correct":"Aurophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"77",
		"question":"Fear of ghosts",
		"choice1":"Gostrophobia",
		"choice2":"Solostrophobia",
		"choice3":"Phasmophobia",
		"choice4":"Pillantrophobia",
		"correct":"Phasmophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"78",
		"question":"Fear of falling in love or being in love",
		"choice1":"Ochlophobia",
		"choice2":"Leteranophobia",
		"choice3":"Logizomechanophobia",
		"choice4":"Philophobia",
		"correct":"Philophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"79",
		"question":"Fear of phobias",
		"choice1":"Phebostrophobia",
		"choice2":"Pherophobia",
		"choice3":"Kataliophobia",
		"choice4":"Phobophobia",
		"correct":"Phobophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"80",
		"question":"Fear of light",
		"choice1":"Acheophobia",
		"choice2":"Photophobia",
		"choice3":"Comestrophobia",
		"choice4":"Demestrophobia",
		"correct":"Photophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"81",
		"question":"Fear of mind",
		"choice1":"Alektrophobia",
		"choice2":"Papyrophobia",
		"choice3":"Psychophobia",
		"choice4":"Colosustrophobia",
		"correct":"Psychophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"82",
		"question":"Fear of flying",
		"choice1":"Fetherophobia",
		"choice2":"Pteromerhanophobia",
		"choice3":"Demestrophobia",
		"choice4":"Calasystophobia",
		"correct":"Pteromerhanophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"83",
		"question":"Fear of puppets",
		"choice1":"Scoleciphobia",
		"choice2":"Pupaphobia",
		"choice3":"Parturiphobia",
		"choice4":"Manequiphobia",
		"correct":"Pupaphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"84",
		"question":"Fear of Fever",
		"choice1":"Pyrexiophobia",
		"choice2":"Pathophobia",
		"choice3":"Pyrophobia",
		"choice4":"Heliophobia",
		"correct":"Pyrexiophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"85",
		"question":"Fear of fire",
		"choice1":"Frenophobia",
		"choice2":"Heliophobia",
		"choice3":"Pyrexiophobia",
		"choice4":"Pyrophobia",
		"correct":"Pyrophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"86",
		"question":"Fear of radiation",
		"choice1":"Ranidaphobia",
		"choice2":"Radiophobia",
		"choice3":"Xelestrophobia",
		"choice4":"Casestrophobia",
		"correct":"Radiophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"87",
		"question":"Fear of frogs",
		"choice1":"Ranidaphobia",
		"choice2":"Reconaphobia",
		"choice3":"Frotestrophobia",
		"choice4":"Himenstrophobia",
		"correct":"Ranidaphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"88",
		"question":"Fear of getting wrinkles",
		"choice1":"Rhytiphobia",
		"choice2":"Wrikostrophobia",
		"choice3":"Retinaphobia",
		"choice4":"Pestophobia",
		"correct":"Rhytiphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"89",
		"question":"Fear of worms",
		"choice1":"Destrophobia",
		"choice2":"Scoleciphobia",
		"choice3":"Cyonephobia",
		"choice4":"Demestrophobia",
		"correct":"Scoleciphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"90",
		"question":"Fear of school",
		"choice1":"Sciophobia",
		"choice2":"Scolionophobia",
		"choice3":"Claustrophobia",
		"choice4":"Emetophobia",
		"correct":"Scolionophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"91",
		"question":"Fear of sharks",
		"choice1":"Iconaphobia",
		"choice2":"Genophobia",
		"choice3":"Selachophobia",
		"choice4":"Fistrophobia",
		"correct":"Selachophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"92",
		"question":"Fear of the moon",
		"choice1":"Lunaphobia",
		"choice2":"Selenophobia",
		"choice3":"Monstrophobia",
		"choice4":"Pherophobia",
		"correct":"Selenophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"93",
		"question":"Fear of the opposite sex",
		"choice1":"Sexophobia",
		"choice2":"Panthophobia",
		"choice3":"Papyrophobia",
		"choice4":"Genophobia",
		"correct":"Sexophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"94",
		"question":"Fear of stars",
		"choice1":"Nomophobia",
		"choice2":"Strostrophobia",
		"choice3":"Celestiophobia",
		"choice4":"Siderophobia",
		"correct":"Siderophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"95",
		"question":"Fear of sleep",
		"choice1":"Somniphobia",
		"choice2":"Equilophobia",
		"choice3":"Dendrophobia",
		"choice4":"Panthophobia",
		"correct":"Somniphobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"96",
		"question":"Fear of learning",
		"choice1":"Sophophobia",
		"choice2":"Centophobia",
		"choice3":"Leteranophobia",
		"choice4":"Nosocomephobia",
		"correct":"Sophophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"97",
		"question":"Fear of outer space",
		"choice1":"Claustrophobia",
		"choice2":"Kleptophobia",
		"choice3":"Peniaphobia",
		"choice4":"Spacephobia",
		"correct":"Spacephobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"98",
		"question":"Fear of narrow things or places",
		"choice1":"Stenophobia",
		"choice2":"Riconstrophobia",
		"choice3":"Felinophobia",
		"choice4":"Limnophobia",
		"correct":"Stenophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"99",
		"question":"Fear of gods or religion",
		"choice1":"Zeustrophobia",
		"choice2":"Theophobia",
		"choice3":"Clasistrophobia",
		"choice4":"Selachophobia",
		"correct":"Theophobia"
	}
	
	];
	
	